Well, how are you all doing?
Do you all remember the video of me playing the very difficult picture Shiritori by myself a long time ago?
I was so surprised when I heard the name of the corner, and this time, since it's so lonely to be alone, I've asked this person to come here to talk about it.
I'm Akari Endo from Juice Juice, Akari.
She's a very good artist. I'm so surprised. It's just like her illustrations.
I have an image of her drawing illustrations rather than copying them, but she draws them all so beautifully.
I know you like to draw, but there's a difference between liking it and being good at it.
Good at
I'm good at it.
I don't think so, I mean... I don't like it.
You know what I mean? You know what I mean? I'll tell you a story.
It's not that I'm not good at it. I'm not good at it.
Yeah, I mean, I guess I like it.
If you like it, that is.
I'd like to start Shiritori right away.
Where do you want to start?
Shiritori nori is a little too conventional, I think.
How about starting with apple nori?
How about starting with nori rin-ringo-nori?
Okay, Kasumi? How about "apple nori"?
Don't write "apple".
Don't write "apple", Ri.
What was he like?
He's a person.
Wow, that's amazing.
A person?
It's not a person.
It's not a person, is it? Yes, it is.
Did I say what kind of person it was?
No, it's not a person.
It's like when I'm eating.
"Doesn't he taste good? I'd say something like...
I'm scared.
Yesterday, Sakura Ishiyama said to me.
"Oh, you're scary!
I think we share the same sensibility.
I'm probably thinking the same thing.
You're probably thinking the same thing.
Yeah, I'm like that.
I'm like, "Oh, my God, I'm like this in the mirror.
Good. I don't think you've been told that enough times yet.
Really?
You're not very good at shiritori.
Oh, you're not good at Shiritori?
I'm not good at Shiritori. I can't think of any.
Heh...
I haven't had a chance to play Shiritori lately.
Sometimes when I do, I really joke around.
The last time I played Shiritori
I couldn't think of the word "pooh".
It's so hard to come up with "pooh".
It's like...
It's like, "Well...
And I can't even think of pudding.
I can't stop thinking about pudding.
I know, it's hard to get rid of it once it's out, isn't it?
You're adding unnecessary things.
Stop being so calm all of a sudden.
You're scaring me.
I'm scared.
What? Oh.
I was wondering if...
I think...
What?
It's complicated.
But maybe it's right.
What if it is?
What? How would I write it?
It's hard to think of just Shiritori.
Yes.
Shiritori is...
You have to think about it in your head.
Whether you can write it or not.
I wrote something weird.
What? Am I wrong?
Am I right?
Oh!
Oh, did I say that?
What's this?
Okay, write it down.
I don't know.
What is it? It's so cool when you write it down.
What?
Oh, I get it!
It's cute.
You can't draw that with my drawing ability!
I can't draw this.
I know what you mean.
Has this part ever floated?
The one that didn't sound at all.
I know what you mean.
I know, I know, I know.
Okay, I kind of get it.
Is it not a sheet?
Something that looks like it.
Oh! Can you draw it?
No, I can't.
I'm getting a little depressed about my drawing ability.
No, you can do it, Inoue-san.
I'll make one that I think will convey the message.I'll go with the one that I think will get the message across.
Yes, sir.
I'm on the edge of my seat.
Say it stylishly. Stylishly.
Fashionably.
Say it stylishly.
Fashionably. Fashionably.
Say it stylishly, stylishly, stylishly
Oh, okay.
Oh, my God, that's great.
Did you really get it?
I got it.
Oh, wow!
Did you have a lot of trouble writing this?
I thought you were going to come up with a masterpiece.
It's all so weird.
What do you mean by weird?
What do you mean?
Like it's not normal.
It's like it's a geek thing.
Not geeky?
Like it wouldn't be bad?
It's not like it's just a picture, but I don't think it's a bad picture.
Pictures?
You're chewing too much, aren't you?
I don't think you can get that from the pictures alone.
It's like it's going to look different.
Oh, really?
Sure, go for it.
If you can't draw or something...
I can't draw anymore.
Want to give it a try?
I've got an idea. I've got a good one.
You want to try it and turn it into something better?
That's great.
What? What? What?
I'm starting to wonder if you got my message.
Oh, no.
Why not? It's all going wrong. It's all wrong.
Can I change it? Sure.
Why? My head is spinning. That's why you can't have esbilicali.
I'm in denial about eslitri. Yes, yes, yes, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
My head's pulling me back to that thing. What do you want me to do?
Can I do the hardest one? I don't know if I can do it.
I don't know if I'm doing okay.
I'm amazed that a hard one even comes to mind in the first place.
I'll never get it.
Really?
Hmm? Hmm?
Hmm?
I don't know.
I don't think that's possible.
No?
Let's not say no.
Say it yourself.
Even if it's not true, you can think about it here.
I don't know what's going on.
What? In my head.
Oh, my God.
I don't know if the words I'm picturing in my head are connected to the picture I'm painting right now.
The words are in my head.
But I don't know if they match what I'm imagining right now.
huh?
From here on out...
Why don't you try to make it end?
Is this scary?
This is what I'm trying to draw now.
It's good.
I don't even know if it's right.
I don't know if I can get that mosaic in here.
I don't even know what's coming through here.
I don't know from here to here.
Okay, okay.
I get it.
Wouldn't it be cool if it ended really nicely?
You and me.
We came up with the best of the best.
It won't end with me.
We'll end it with the next apple.
You're thinking the same thing as before.
I'm thinking the same thing.
What?
Please let them know that I'll finish next time.
Next time.
Look me in the eye.
What?
Come here, come here.
Come here.
Here.
Fensh!
Stylish, right?
Fashionable?
I don't know.
Fashionable... yes.Stylish... yeah.
There are so many concepts of fashionable.
Well...
Is it the same as what you said at the time?
Aah! Yes.
I guess so.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's okay.
You don't have to think about anything. It's really the opposite.
It's beautiful.
It's fine.
Is it?
It's not at all what I expected.
Of course it is.
What's this?
What is this?
It's starting to fall apart.
It's good.
I've been thinking... since we got here.
I knew from the moment we got here that it wasn't going to fall apart.
Oh, yeah.
As expected.
Yes, as expected, it's falling apart.
As soon as I saw this, I thought, "Wow, this is really good.
This one is cute, too.
I thought, "This one's cute too, like the ones I always draw.
And then it started to fall apart.
It's getting hard to tell, isn't it?
Compared to Inoue-san's drawings, my drawings are a mess.
Yeah, it kind of stopped here.
That's right.
I'll never understand it.
It's for something.
I have a lot of them.
But how many?
Bullet points.
What do you call this one? This one? What do you call this one? Some of them are...
They're not connected.
Is that katakana with the extension at the end?
Yes.
Can I draft it again?
I haven't touched it much. I got it. I got it.
Well, can I develop a new word? No.
End it nicely. It's never going to end this way, because it doesn't have to end here.
It doesn't have to end here.
What is this?
I went all the way through this. I went all the way through it.
I got an idea. I'm glad.
What did you come up with?
I'm sure I won't make it to the end.
What did you say?
It's up to you, Inoue-san.
It's over, Watan.
He's lost it. He's lost it.
You're screwed.
Researching.
No results found.
Oh, I won.
I'll make sure it's the next one that doesn't end up here.
With this appropriateness.
It's okay. We probably can't get any better than this.
Go for it.
It doesn't have to end.
I'll finish it.
Who? It's not a person, is it?
Who? Who are you?
Who are you?
Come on.
What?
What? Really?
Huh! I'm done! It's over!
It's over!
Yeah!
I finally changed!
Let's get to the explanation!
What's this?
Squirrel!
Nice!
Watermelon!
Pirate!
There it is!
Spider!
Was it this one?
Mole!
Rice!
I've got a glitch here...
What was the first thing you were going to write?
Rice...
I thought of scombs.
There are many members of the Laminaria family.
There are many kinds of kikurage.
And you thought of kikurage.
The jellyfish pulled me in.
Then I thought of a tree.
Did I write "tree"?
Oh, no! It's not a fungus! I thought.
I'll never use it.
It's too hard to convey.Too hard to tell.
I thought it was in Scombe.
And then I thought, "Skomb...
It's a scomb!
I thought it was rice.
I thought it was rice vermicelli.
Aah!
I wrote "eye" because I thought it was a spiny lobster.
And a scalpel!
I figured it out!
Isn't that amazing?
You figured it out.
Soup!
It's a Phillips-head screwdriver.
But seriously, I didn't know what it was.
But then I found out it's a screwdriver.
A screwdriver!
I thought it was something else.
I thought, "Where did this all start? I thought...
It's a screwdriver! I thought it was...
Basketball.
Roulette.
Okay, okay.
Tonka.
Okay, I got it.
Cheese.
Pants.
Not very pretty at all.
Good-bye.